Indiana University President's Office records, 1937-1962 C213
Indiana University Archives
- Subject files, 1937-1962
  - Foreign Students Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 133)
  - Committee to Aid Foreign Students (Box 133)
  - Fraternity Counselors Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 133)
  - Fund Raising Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 133)
  - Committee on Final Grades of Graduating Students, 1946-1947 (Box 134)
  - Graduate Committee, 1951-1956 (Box 134)
  - Committee on Graduation, 1943-1944 (Box 134)
  - Committee to Pass on Grant Applications, 1949-1950 (Box 134)
  - Committee on Group Insurance, 1944-1945 (Box 134)
  - Halls of Residence Committee, 1943-1959; (18 folders) (Box 134)
  - High School-College Relations Committee (Box 134)
  - How to Finance Higher Education-Steering Committee for Study of, 1958-1959 (Box 134)
  - Committee on Industrial Research Location (Box 134)
  - Committee on Insurance and Retirement, 1946-1950; (5 folders) (Box 134)
  - Inter-American Affairs Committee, 1940-1944; (3 folders) (Box 134)
  - Inter-Institutional Study Committee (Box 134)
  - Committee to Interpret University Needs and Policies to the Public, 1948-1949 (Box 134)
  - Interpretation of the War Effort Committee (Box 134)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 134)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 134)
  - Committee Studying Questions Involving Student Health Services, 1950-1951 (Box 134)
  - Committee on Health Hazards in Use of Radioactive Materials, 1948-1952; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Student Health Service Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 134)
  - Committee on Hospital Equipment, 1944-1945 (Box 134)
  - Committee on Interdepartmental Studies in Human Development and Technology (Box 134)
  - Committee on Late Enrollment and Late Registration, 1943-1944 (Box 134)
  - Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America, 1939-1940 (Box 134)
  - Committee on Leaves of Absence, 1943-1944 (Box 134)
  - Committee to work out details of a planning program and to serve as liaison between I.U. and Indiana Economic Council, 1946-1947 (Box 134)
  - Library Committee (Box 134)
  - Committee on Branch Science Libraries (Box 134)
  - Library Committee of the Women's Residence Center, 1943-1944 (Box 134)
  - Committee to Study the Question of a Program for Management Training, 1943-1945; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Citizens Committee for the Marshall Plan, 1947-1948 (Box 134)
  - Motion Picture Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 134)
  - National Thrift Committee (Box 134)
  - Parking Committee, 1943-1952; (2 folders) (Box 134)
  - Faculty-Staff Committee on Parking Report (Box 134)
  - Committee on Patten Foundation, 1943-1944 (Box 135)
  - Committee on Physical Fitness, 1943-1945; (2 folders) (Box 135)
  - Physical Plant Facilities Committee (Box 135)
  - Postwar Music Committee, 1947-1948 (Box 135)
  - Postwar Planning Committee, 1942-1946; (15 folders) (Box 135)
  - Committee on Promotions, 1943-1944 (Box 135)
  - Summer Session Committee on Promotion and Publicity, 1950-1951 (Box 135)
  - Publications Committee, 1943-1951; (4 folders) (Box 135)
  - Committee on Public Debt Policy, 1946-1952; (7 folders) (Box 135)
  - Public Relations Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 135)
  - Publicity Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 135)
  - Radio Committee, 1943-1944; 1951-1953; (3 folders) (Box 135)
  - Recreation Committee, 1947-1951; (2 folders) (Box 135)
  - Committees on the Role of the University in a Democratic Society, 1947-1948 (Box 135)
  - Committee on Rumor Clinic, 1943-1944 (Box 135)
  - Committee on Sabbatical Leaves, 1944-1945 (Box 135)
  - Safety Committee, 1949-1953; (6 folders) (Box 135)
  - Schedule Committee, 1943-1947; (2 folders) (Box 135)
  - Committee on Scholarships and Student Aid, 1938-1947; (7 folders) (Box 135)
  - Presidency Search Committee, 1937 (Box 135A)
  - Committee on Scholarships, 1946-1959; (20 folders) (Box 136)
  - Committee on Usage of Smithwood vs. Tower for Summer Students and Conferences, 1960-1961 (Box 136)
  - Social Affairs Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 136)
  - Social Committee Report for I.U., 1943-1944 (Box 136)
  - Space Committee File, 1956-1957 (Box 136)
  - Space Committee, 1955-1962; (8 folders) (Box 137)
  - Committees to Study the Speech Clinic Set-Up of the University, 1949-1950 (Box 137)
  - Safety Recreational Program Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 137)
  - Committee on the Place of Statistics and Statistical Method in the University, 1943-1952; (2 folders) (Box 137)
  - Student Affairs Committee, 1943-1945; (2 folders) (Box 137)
  - Committee on Student Employment, 1942-1944; (3 folders) (Box 137)
  - Student Health Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 137)
  - Student Refugee Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 137)
  - Tax Committee Meeting, May 8, 1940 (Box 137)
  - Graduate Study Questionnaire Committee of Thirteen, 1939-1952; (14 folders) (Box 137)
  - Committee on Training Vocational Counselors, 1943-1945; (2 folders) (Box 137)
  - Committee on University Structure and Educational Policy-Subcommittee on Budgets (Box 137)
  - Committee on Victory Gardens (Box 137)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 137)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 137)
  - Committees, Miscellaneous, 1949-1954; (5 folders) (Box 137)
  - Committees, Miscellaneous, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 138)
  - Commercial Teachers' Conference, 1939-1940 (Box 138)
  - Commons and Soda Shop, 1938-1939 (Box 138)
  - Communicators-Two-Way, 1940-1941 (Box 138)
  - Communism, 1946-1953; (14 folders) (Box 138)
  - Communism Investigation, 1946-1947; (7 folders) (Box 138)
  - Communist Party, 1947-1948 (Box 138)
  - Community Chest, 1938-1939 (Box 138)
  - Community Chest Fund, 1939-1947; (3 folders) (Box 138)
  - Community Services (Box 138)
  - Complaints and Criticisms, Letters of (Box 138)
  - Competitive Scholarships, 1939-1940 (Box 138)
  - Comptroller's Office Reports, 1937-1943; (9 folders) (Box 138)
  - Con, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 138)
  - Con, 1941-1962; (20 folders) (Box 139)
  - Conant, James B., Committee suggested to recommend men for the position in Chemistry, Physics, Geology, and Botany, 1937-1938 (Box 139)
  - Concessions, Indiana University, 1948-1951; (4 folders) (Box 139)
  - Concessions, 1950-1962; (31 folders) (Box 140)
  - Conference Bureau, 1957-1958 (Box 140)
  - Conferences, Institutes, Workshops, etc., 1958-1959 (Box 140)
  - Conferences, Meetings, etc., 1959-1960 (Box 140)
  - English and Foreign Language Conference, March 17-19, 1961 (Box 140)
  - Conference for High School Teachers of Science, April 3, 1954 (Box 140)
  - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1952-1958; (3 folders) (Box 140)
  - Currently Scheduled Conferences, 1958-1959 (Box 140)
  - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1957-1962; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Conference Bureau, 1958-1960; (2 folders) (Box 140)
  - Conference and Conventions Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Box 140)
  - Conference of Small Business Organizations, 1945-1946 (Box 140)
  - Conference on Planning Post-War School Buildings, 1944-1946 (Box 140)
  - Foreign Policy Conference, 1950-1958 (Box 140)
  - Conference on Problems of American Foreign Policy, 1959-1962; (2 folders) (Box 140)
  - Conference on Pupil Transportation and Related Problems in Non-Urban Education in Indiana, 1945-1946 (Box 140)
  - Conference at State Department with Robert Thayer re: Puerto Rican Cultural Center, January 4, 1961 (Box 140)
  - Conference on the Superior Student (Box 140)
  - Congress on Education Here, 1939-1940 (Box 140)
  - Congressional Delegation from Indiana re: N.Y.A., 1938-1939 (Box 140)
  - Conklin, Prof. E.S., 1937-1949; (5 folders) (Box 140)
  - Conn, 1937-1949; (7 folders) (Box 140)
  - Conn, 1949-1955; (2 folders) (Box 141)
  - Conn, Kenneth E., 1952-1953 (Box 141)
  - Conr, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 141)
  - Conservation State Department and Zoology Department-Cooperation Committee, 1937-1938 (Box 141)
  - Conservation Education, 1952-1959 (Box 141)
  - Conservation Workshop, 1953-1955; (2 folders) (Box 141)
  - Indiana University Conservative League - Speech by Rep. Donald Jackson and film in defence of the House Un-American Activities Committee, 1960-1961 (Box 141)
  - Constitution Day Committee, 1945-1948; (3 folders) (Box 141)
  - Construction (Box 141)
  - General (Box 141)
    - Analysis of Voucher Pmts. on all new PWA buildings on campus (Box 141)
    - Army Quonset Huts, 1946 (Box 141)
    - Business Adm. Building, 1936-1940 (Box 141)
    - School of Business Bldg., work papers for analysis of contract and equipment contracts (Box 141)
    - School of Business Bldg.-A. Sugarman claim, 1940-1942 (Box 141)
    - School of Business Bldg., Weekly Payroll-A. Sugarman, 1939-1940 (Box 141)
    - Information on Dormitories (Box 141)
    - Inventory, Planning, 1953-1954 (Box 141)
    - Payments, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 141)
    - Physical Science Building, 1938-1942; (3 folders) (Box 141)
    - Planning Report, Part 1 pp. 1-173, 1959 (Box 141)
      Note: Building floors plans excluded from scans (contact IU Archives for access)
    - Planning Report, Part 2 pp. 181-429, 1959 (Box 141)
  - Construction Planning Report, July 1955 (Box 142)
  - Construction Specifications for New Buildings, 1939 (Box 142)
  - Contemporary Club of Indianapolis, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 142)
  - Continental Classroom, 1958-1962; (4 folders) (Box 142)
  - Controller (Box 142)
  - Controllers Institute of America, 1938-1939 (Box 142)
  - Controversy - Communism, Freedom, etc., 1940-1941 (Box 142)
  - Convocation Committee, 1937-1943; (2 folders) (Box 142)
  - University Convocations Two-Year Report, 1942-1944 (Box 142)
  - Convocation Committee, 1944-1947; (3 folders) (Box 142)
  - Convocations Annual Report, 1948-1949 (Box 142)
  - Chairman of Convocations Annual Report, 1949-1950 (Box 142)
  - Committee on Convocations Annual Report, 1950-1951 (Box 142)
  - Chairman of Convocations Annual Report, 1952-1953 (Box 142)
  - Convocation Series Annual Report, 1953-1960; (7 folders) (Box 142)
  - President's Annual Convocations Report (Box 142)
  - Convocation Series Annual Report, 1960-1961 (Box 142)
  - Convocations, 1961-1962 (Box 142)
  - Coo, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 142)
  - Cook, H.H., 1951-1961 (Box 142)
  - Cook, Mary Ellen-Notes concerning Board Meetings, 1937-1938 (Box 142)
  - Cookson, Thomas A., 1937-1952; (15 folders) (Box 143)
  - Coon, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 143)
  - Cooper, Ida Mae - Lease, Lot 11 in Latonia Park Subdivision of Vanarsdall's Addition to Irvington for Gardening Purposes, 1945 (Box 143)
  - Cooper, Kent (Box 143)
  - Cooperation-Coordination and Regionalization on Education, 1939-1943; (3 folders) (Box 143)
  - Cooperative Housing, 1941-1942 (Box 143)
  - Cooperative Extension Program, 1945 (Box 143)
  - Bureau of Cooperative Research and Field Service, 1937-1945; (3 folders) (Box 143)
  - Division of Research and Field Service of the School of Education, 1949-1960; (12 folders) (Box 143)
  - Cop, 1947-1955; (8 folders) (Box 143)
  - Copernician Convocation, 1941-1942 (Box 143)
  - Cor, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 143)
  - Core Program, 1957-1960 (Box 143)
  - Corn, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 143)
  - Cornell University Ithaca, N.Y., 1937-1962; (22 folders) (Box 144)
  - Corr, Edwin, 1937-1940; (4 folders) (Box 144)
  - Corr, Henry Injury Case, 1939-1940 (Box 144)
  - Cortazar, Roberto, 1940-1941 (Box 144)
  - Cos, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 144)
  - Cosmopolitan Club, 1939-1961 (Box 144)
  - Cosmopolitan Club International Dinner, Alumni Hall, Union Building, October 28, 1956 (Box 144)
  - Cost Per Credit Hour Study, 1941-1942 (Box 144)
  - Costs-Comparison of in Indiana University, 1939-1940 (Box 144)
  - Cot, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 144)
  - Cou, 1937-1955; (13 folders) (Box 144)
  - Coulter, J.G.-Book, 1940-1941 (Box 144)
  - Coulter, John Merle (Portrait), 1940-1942 (Box 144)
  - Council for Economic Growth and Security, Inc., 1961-1962; (2 folders) (Box 144)
  - Council of Eight, 1961-1962 (Box 144)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education, Inc., 1954-1959; (6 folders) (Box 144)
    - Seminar on College Finances, October 23, 24, 25, 1958 (Box 144)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education, Inc., 1959-1962; (4 folders) (Box 145)
  - Council for Inter-American Cooperation, Inc., 1945-1948; (3 folders) (Box 145)
  - Council of State Governments (Box 145)
    - 1954-1961, (7 folders) (Box 145)
    - Interstate Committee on Higher Education, Chicago, Illinois, May, 1957 (Box 145)
    - Midwestern Regional Conference Cleveland, Ohio, July, 1957 (Box 145)
  - Council of Ten (Box 145)
    - 1951 - March 1952 (Box 145)
    - April 1952 (Box 145)
    - May - July 1952 (Box 145)
    - August - November 1952 (Box 145)
    - December 1952 (Box 145)
    - Minutes, December 1951 - April 1957 (Box 145)
    - January - February 1953 (Box 145)
    - March - April 1953 (Box 145)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 145)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 145)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 145)
  - Council of Ten (Box 145a)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 145a)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 145a)
    - 1958-1959 (Box 145a)
    - 1959-1960 (Box 145a)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1959-1960 (Box 145a)
  - Council of Ten, 1960-1962; (5 folders) (Box 146)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1943-1955; (20 folders) (Box 146)
  - Council on Foreign Relations, 1955-1962; (14 folders) (Box 147)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc., 1957-1960; (9 folders) (Box 147)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc., 1960-1962; (21 folders) (Box 148)
  - Council on Library Resources, Inc., 1961-1962; (2 folders) (Box 149)
  - Council of State Governments-Interstate Committee on Higher Education, 1955-1956 (Box 149)
  - Counseling, 1947-1958; (2 folders) (Box 149)
  - Counseling Office Annual Report (Box 149)
    - 1947-1948 (Box 149)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 149)
    - 1953-1954 (Box 149)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 149)
    - 1955-1956 (Box 149)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 149)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 149)
  - Counselors, 1943-1944 (Box 149)
  - Counsilman, James E. (Doc), 1957-1961 (Box 149)
  - County Scholarships, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 149)
  - Cov, 1937-1962; (23 folders) (Box 149)
  - Cow, 1948-1953; (5 folders) (Box 149)
  - Cox, 1937-1955; (18 folders) (Box 149)
  - Cox, Ralph - Case, 1944-1945 (Box 149)
  - Cr, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 149)
  - Cr, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 150)
  - Cra, 1941-1942 (Box 150)
  - Craig, C.C.-Institute of Mathematical Statistics, 1939-1940 (Box 150)
  - Craig, George, 1949-1959; (7 folders) (Box 150)
  - Craig, Mrs. Mary Brown, 1943-1960; (16 folders) (Box 150)
  - Craig, Mary Brown, 1960-1961 (Box 151)
  - Cran, 1946-1950; (4 folders) (Box 151)
  - Crane, President A.G. Address: You and Radio, 1938-1939 (Box 151)
  - Crane, Indiana, 1953-1962; (9 folders) (Box 151)
  - Crank File-Letters, 1937-1962; (23 folders) (Box 151)
  - Cravens, Mrs. Mellie G., 1942-1952; (11 folders) (Box 151)
  - Cravens, Oscar H. Newspaper clippings and correspondence (Box 151)
  - Craw, 1948-1955; (7 folders) (Box 151)
  - Cre, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 151)
  - Creative Writing, 1939-1941; (2 folders) (Box 151)
  - Credit for Military Service, 1942-1949; (8 folders) (Box 151)
  - Credit Union, 1955-1962; (2 folders) (Box 151)
  - Cri, 1952-1955; (3 folders) (Box 152)
  - Critic Teachers, 1939-1942; (3 folders) (Box 152)
  - Criticisms, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 152)
  - Cro, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 152)
  - CROP (Christian Rural Overseas Program), 1949-1951; (2 folders) (Box 152)
  - Cros, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 152)
  - Cross, Dr. S.H.-Luncheon, 1939-1940 (Box 152)
  - Crossland, Dorothy E., 1959 (Box 152)
  - Cru, 1950-1955; (5 folders) (Box 152)
  - Crusade for Freedom, 1950-1956; (4 folders) (Box 152)
  - Cu, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 152)
  - Cu, 1946-1962; (16 folders) (Box 153)
  - Cuffey, Dr. James Astronomer, 1937-1938 (Box 153)
  - Cultural Offerings and Attendance (Box 153)
  - Culver Family History of Members, 1940-1941 (Box 153)
  - Culver Military Academy Culver, Indiana, 1937-1958; (17 folders) (Box 153)
  - Cumings, Prof. E.R., 1937-1944; (8 folders) (Box 153)
  - Cunningham, Alex, 1939-1940 (Box 153)
  - Cur, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 153)
  - Curriculum - Additions and Changes, 1942-1947; (5 folders) (Box 153)
  - Curriculum - Additions and Changes, 1947-1962; (17 folders) (Box 154)
  - Curriculum Comparison, 1941-1943 (Box 154)
  - Curriculum Committee (Permanent) Appointed by State Board of Education, 1939-1940 (Box 154)
  - Curry, 1938-1962 (Box 154)
  - Cus, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 154)
  - Cuzzort, R.P. (Box 154)
  - Cyclotron, 1938-1950; (2 folders) (Box 154)
    - Facility, 1955-1962 (Box 154)
  - Cyprus (Box 154)
  - D, 1937-1947; (10 folders) (Box 154)
  - D, 1947-1962; (15 folders) (Box 155)
  - Dad's Association of I.U., 1939-1944; (5 folders) (Box 155)
  - Dads Day, 1941-1942; (3 folders) (Box 155)
  - Daggett, Robert Frost, 1937-1938 (Box 155)
  - Dahle, Casper O., 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 155)
  - Dal, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 155)
  - Dan, 1938-1951; (13 folders) (Box 155)
  - Dan, 1951-1962; (11 folders) (Box 156)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1945-1962; (2 folders) (Box 156)
  - Daniels, Arthur S., 1956-1962 (Box 156)
  - Dar, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 156)
  - Dargan House, 1938-1948 (Box 156)
  - Dargan, Samuel, 1938-1948 (Box 156)
  - Dat, 1948-1950; (2 folders) (Box 156)
  - Dauber's Club, 1937-1938 (Box 156)
  - Dav, 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 156)
  - Davis, H.T.-Loan, 1940-1941 (Box 156)
  - Davis, Prof. R.C. Report made on salaries & promotions, 1937-1938 (Box 156)
  - Davis, Walter A., 1943-1944 (Box 156)
  - Dav, 1947-1948 (Box 156)
  - Dav, 1948-1955; (7 folders) (Box 157)
  - Davis, 1948-1955; (7 folders) (Box 157)
  - Davis, Ritchie Gilruth, 1948-1962 (Box 157)
  - Dav, 1955-1962; (7 folders) (Box 157)
  - Davis Medical Foundation, 1956-1957 (Box 157)
    - Fourth Annual Meeting, 1958-1959 (Box 157)
  - Davie, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 157)
  - Daw, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 157)
  - Daw Kyi Kyi (Box 157)
  - Day, 1937-1945; (8 folders) (Box 157)
  - Day, 1945-1955; (10 folders) (Box 158)
  - Day, David I., 1949-1952; (3 folders) (Box 158)
  - Day, Harry G., 1939-1940 (Box 158)
  - Day, Mrs. Wilma - Case Disability, 1938-1939 (Box 158)
  - Dec, 1954-1955 (Box 158)
  - De, 1937-1954; (17 folders) (Box 158)
  - De, 1954-1962; (8 folders) (Box 159)
  - Dea, 1945-1955; (10 folders) (Box 159)
  - Deal, Paul, 1938-1939 (Box 159)
  - Dean, Everett S. (Box 159)
  - Dean, Joel P., 1937-1938 (Box 159)
  - Research Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 159)
  - Dean of Faculties, 1956-1959; (3 folders) (Box 159)
  - Dean of Men - Applications, 1939-1942 (Box 159)
  - Dean of Men Office Five-Year Report, 1937-1942 (Box 159)
  - Dean of Men Office Two-Year Report, 1942-1944 (Box 159)
  - Dean of Men Annual Report, 1937-1946 (Box 159)
    - 1937-1938 (Box 159)
    - 1938-1939 (Box 159)
    - 1939-1940 (Box 159)
    - 1940-1941 (Box 159)
    - 1942-1943 (Box 159)
    - 1944-1945 (Box 159)
    - 1945-1946 (Box 159)
  - Dean of Students, 1945-1962; (7 folders) (Box 159)
    - Annual Report, 1947-1951; (3 folders) (Box 159)
  - Deans - Academic, 1937-1959; (22 folders) (Box 159)
  - Deans - Academic, 1959-1962; (3 folders) (Box 160)
  - Deans and Heads, 1954-1963; (27 folders) (Box 160)
  - Deans and Others' Reports for Year, 1939-1945; (5 folders) (Box 160)
  - Notices to Deans and Heads of Departments, 1941-1942 (Box 160)
  - Deans Meetings, 1952-1962; (10 folders) (Box 160)
  - Death-Payments to Widows Upon Death of Faculty or Staff, 1939-1940 (Box 160)
  - Dec, 1937-1940; (4 folders) (Box 160)
  - Dee, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 160)
  - Deferred Fees-Reinstatements Etc., 1938-1939 (Box 160)
  - Defense Bonds, 1941-1943; (2 folders) (Box 160)
  - Defense Training, 1941-1942 (Box 160)
  - Deferred Fees, 1939-1942; (3 folders) (Box 160)
  - DeFrantz, Faburne, E., 1956 (Box 160)
  - Degree Comparison with Purdue, 1955-1956 (Box 160)
  - Degrees, 1939-1962; (17 folders) (Box 160)
    - Examinations for Doctor of Philosophy Degree, 1951-1953; (2 folders) (Box 160)
  - Degrees - Examinations for Doctor of Philosophy Degree, 1953-1962; (14 folders) (Box 161)
  - DeHaven, I.C. Engineering Co. RE: Cochrane Steam Flow Meters, 1937-1938 (Box 161)
  - Del, 1937-1945; (8 folders) (Box 161)
  - Del, 1945-1962; (17 folders) (Box 162)
  - Delgado, Francisco A., 1939-1957 (Box 162)
    (Includes The Philippine Collegian, October 19, 1939 )
  - Delinquent List - Ruling of Trustees, 1939-1941; (2 folders) (Box 162)
  - Delivanis, D., 1949-1953; (4 folders) (Box 162)
  - Delta Chi, 1938-1954 (Box 162)
  - Delta Sigma Theta, 1947-1956 (Box 162)
  - Democracy - Course on, 1940-1941 (Box 162)
  - Den, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 162)
  - Dental Association of Indiana, 1939-1940 (Box 162)
  - School of Dentistry (Box 162)
    - Five-Year report, 1937-1942 (Box 162)
    - Annual report (Box 162)
      - 1937-1938 (Box 162)
      - 1938-1939 (Box 162)
      - 1939-1940 (Box 162)
      - 1944-1945 (Box 162)
      - 1945-1946 (Box 162)
      - 1946-1947 (Box 162)
      - 1948-1949 (Box 162)
      - 1949-1950 (Box 162)
      - 1950-1951 (Box 162)
      - 1951-1952 (Box 162)
      - 1952-1953 (Box 162)
      - 1953-1954 (Box 162)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 162)
      - 1955-1956 (Box 162)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 162)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 162)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 162)
      - 1959-1960 (Box 162)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 162)
      - 1961-1962 (Box 162)
  - University of Denver - Opinion Research Center, 1948-1949 (Box 162)
  - Dep, 1946-1947 (Box 162)
  - Departmental Lectures, 1939-1943; (4 folders) (Box 163)
  - DePauw Cooperative Program (Box 163)
  - DePauw University, 1937-1962; (25 folders) (Box 163)
  - Depositories - Public, 1938-1961; (8 folders) (Box 163)
  - Der, 1937-1941; (4 folders) (Box 163)
  - Deshais, Arthur, 1952-1955 (Box 163)
  - Det, 1941-1962; (21 folders) (Box 163)
  - Detzer, Karl, 1939-1940 (Box 163)
  - Dev, 1945-1955; (10 folders) (Box 163)
  - De Voto the Literacy Fallacy Criticism, 1943-1944 (Box 163)
  - Dew (Box 163)
  - Di, 1937-1943; (6 folders) (Box 163)
  - Di, 1943-1962; (19 folders) (Box 164)
  - Dic, 1948-1949 (Box 164)
  - Dick, 1952-1955; (3 folders) (Box 164)
  - Dickey, Marcus, 1938-1951; (6 folders) (Box 164)
  - Die, 1937-1940; (3 folders) (Box 164)
  - Diet, 1939-1940 (Box 164)
  - Dieterlie, D. Lyle (2 folders) (Box 164)
  - Dietians-Student Courses, 1939-1940 (Box 164)
  - Difco Laboratories, 1939-1940 (Box 164)
  - Dil, 1937-1945; (8 folders) (Box 164)
  - Dil, 1945-1962; (17 folders) (Box 165)
  - Dillon, John H., 1937-1946; (9 folders) (Box 165)
  - Dillon, Lee, 1938-1939 (Box 165)
  - Diplomas, 1938-1940; (2 folders) (Box 165)
  - Diploma Letters, 1940-1948; (12 folders) (Box 165)
  - Diploma Letters, 1947-1948 (Box 166)
  - Diplomas Sent, 1947-1948; (3 folders) (Box 166)
  - Diploma Letters, 1948-1950; (6 folders) (Box 166)
  - Diplomas-Miscellaneous, 1949-1951; (2 folders) (Box 166)
  - Diploma Letters, 1950-1951; (3 folders) (Box 166)
  - Diplomas-Miscellaneous, 1951-1952 (Box 166)
  - Diploma Letters, 1951-1952; (2 folders) (Box 166)
  - Diploma Letters, 1951-1953; (4 folders) (Box 167)
  - Diploma Half-Sheets-Miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 167)
  - Diploma Letters, 1953-1954; (3 folders) (Box 167)
  - Diploma Half-Sheets-Miscellaneous, 1953-1956; (2 folders) (Box 167)
  - Diploma Letters, 1955-1957; (6 folders) (Box 167)
  - Diploma Receipts, 1957-1958 (Box 167)
  - Diploma Letters, 1957-1961; (12 folders) (Box 167)
  - Director of Admissions Applications, 1937-1938 (Box 167)
  - Directory-Indiana University, 1938-1939 (Box 167)
  - Directory Board in Administration Building, 1938-1939 (Box 167)
  - Directories, 1944-1947; (3 folders) (Box 167)
  - Disciplinary Matters, 1957-1958 (Box 167)
  - Distinguished Alumni Service Award, 1959-1961; (2 folders) (Box 167)
  - Distinguished Service Professorship, 1956-1961; (4 folders) (Box 167)
  - Distributive Occupations, 1937-1945; (7 folders) (Box 167)